

Harsha Prajapati

886-174-1035 | E: harshap744@gmail.com

Flat No 221, Radiant Silver Bell 2 ,3rd Cross Road, Kodigehalli , Kadugodi,

Banglore, Karnataka 560067

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced System Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry and Passionate Front End Web Developer with 3.3 years of experience working in different projects of Ui development and enhancement and

To keep up with the Front-end web Development technologies. I want to use my skills in the best possible way for achieving the company's goals and keep on learning.

SKILLS

- Html5
- Css3
- Javascript
- Jquery basics

- Angular 7
- Bootstrap 4
- Sql basics

WORK HISTORY

SYSTEM ENGINEER

09/2018 to CURRENT

TCS | Bengaluru, Karnataka

Organisation- Rolls Royce Digital

Development Project- Front End Web Developer

Technical Insights- I designed the Ui for this application and also worked on the functionality using Javascript, Html5, Css3, bootstrap, Ajax and KendoUi. Candyspace- Using Angular 7 framework I designed the Ui for application, and have worked on Data binding for the grid, created Services. Tools used were Visual studio code and Visual studio.

SYSTEM ENGINEER

11/2017 to 08/2018

Tcs - Organization : Lafarge Holcim | Bangalore, Karnataka

- Support Project -Here for a Dispatching Cement application solved problem tickets for any bug in the application by debugging the code, giving solutions in the code or executing queries in the backend in sql.
- Tools used were Visual Studio, Service Now and Sql Management.

ASSISTANT SYSTEM ENGINEER

08/2016 to 08/2017

Tcs - Organization: Intel | Bangalore, Karnataka

- Ui development I worked on the Ui development using Angular Js , Html, Css.
- It was an existing application where the client had asked us to redesign it in a single page application and modify the html pages and add different functionalities to it.
 - Tools used were Notepad ++.
- Enhancement Project Worked on Problem tickets using C# for front end in

- Visual studio and for backend have used Sql.
- Here I worked on Change Requests given by the clients to make changes in the front end Ui or to make a new functionality in the device and execute queries in the backend using sql.

EDUCATION ()

Btech Biotechnology

04/2016

GITAM University, Visakhapatnam, AP

focused in Biotechnology

AWARDS AND ACHIEVEMENTS

- Got the best team Award- Award for excellence in Lafarge Holcim.
- On Hacker Earth participated in challenges using skills in Javascript, Json, Ajax calls, html and css to complete the problem statement and have cleared it.
- In college fest have won 1st position for Green Innovation event.

TRAINING AND CERTIFICATIONS

- External Certification done in Front End Web Developer I Nanodegree in Udacity.
- Digital Competencies in IEvolve for AngualrJs, Html, Css and Bootstrap.
- Learner on Hacker earth, have solved problem statements on it .
- Active learner on TreeHouse for learning different tracks on Front End Web Development, Intermediate C#, Full stack Javascript, APIs, responsive layouts
- Completed trainings in C# asp.Net and sql.